Finding Aid for the Norman Cousins Papers LSC.1385
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Volume 2
  - Document Case #181 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1958
    - 8. Folder. KO-KT (Box 343)
    - 9. Folder. KU-KZ (Box 343)
    - 10. Folder. LA-LD (Box 343)
    - 11. Folder. La Salle, Illinois - Itinerary -, Oct. 24 (Box 343)
    - 12. Folder. Lasker (Box 343)
    - 13. Folder. LE-LH (Box 343)
    - 14. Folder. Levin, Martin (Box 343)
    - 15. Folder. LI-LN (Box 343)
    - 16. Folder. Lists (Box 343)
  - Document Case #182 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1958
    - 1. Folder. LO-LT (Box 343)
    - 2. Folder. Lowman, Eleanor S. (Box 343)
    - 3. Folder. LU-LZ (Box 343)
    - 4. Folder. Luce, Henry R. (Box 343)
    - 5. Folder. Mac (Box 343)
    - 6. Folder. Macmillan Company (Box 343)
    - 7. Folder. McGraw - Hill (Box 343)
    - 8. Folder. Manhattan, Kansas - Itinerary -, Oct. 7 (Box 343)
    - 9. Folder. March's Thesaurus (Box 343)
    - 10. Folder. Comments on Thesaurus (Box 343)
    - 11. Folder. Mc (Box 343)
    - 12. Folder. MA-MD (Box 343)
    - 13. Folder. Marshall, David (Box 343)
    - 14. Folder. ME-MH (Box 343)
    - 15. Folder. Menuhin, Yehudi (Box 343)
    - 16. Folder. MI-MN (Box 343)
  - Document Case #183 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1958
    - 1. Folder. Minneapolis, Minn. Itinerary - UWF Convention -, May 23-25 (Box 343)
    - 2. Folder. Minneapolis, Minn. Itinerary -, October 23 (Box 343)
    - 3. Folder. MO-MT (Box 343)
    - 4. Folder. Mount Holyoke, S. Hadley Mass. - Itinerary -, June 1 (Box 343)
    - 5. Folder. MU-MZ (Box 343)
    - 6. Folder. NA-ND (Box 343)
    - 7. Folder. National Planning Assoc. #1 (Jerry Spingarn) (Box 343)
    - 8. Folder. National Planning Assoc. #2 (Jerry Spingarn) (Box 343)
    - 9. Folder. National Federation of the Blind (Box 343)
    - 10. Folder. Nationwide Insurance (Box 343)
  - Document Case # 184 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1958
    - 1. Folder. NE-NH (Box 343)
    - 2. Folder. N.E.A. (Box 343)
    - 3. Folder. Nevins, Allan: Dinner (Box 343)
    - 4. Folder. New Jersey Teacher, In Re (Hersey's"Hiroshima") (Box 343)
    - 5. Folder. New School (Citizens Comm) (Box 343)
    - 6. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - World Day of Prayer, February 21 (Box 343)
    - 7. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - Carnegie Endowment, February 22 (Box 343)
    - 8. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - Museum of Modern Art, February 26 (Box 343)
    - 9. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - Hotel Plaza, February 28 (Box 343)
    - 10. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - -New York Teachers Guild, March 1 (Box 343)
    - 11. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - Japan Society, March 7 (Box 343)
    - 12. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - India Society, March 22 (Box 343)
    - 13. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - Human Relations Workshop, March 31 (Box 343)
    - 14. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - "Open Mind" - TV, April 6 (Box 343)
    - 15. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - All Souls' Church, April 7 (Box 343)
    - 16. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - Collegiate Council for U.N., April 20 (Box 343)
    - 17. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - New School, Oct. 21 (Box 343)
    - 18. Folder. New York City - Itinerary - - ChristChurch, Nov. 12 (Box 343)
    - 19. Folder. No. Carolina, Univ. of(Bur. of Public Records Collection & Res.) (Box 343)
      (N.C. is Hon. member Adv. Bd.)
    - 20. Folder. NI-NN (Box 343)
    - 21. Folder. NO-NT (Box 343)
    - 22. Folder. Norwalk, Conn. - Itinerary-, Sept. 5 (Box 343)
  - Document Case #185 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1958
    - 1. Folder. OA-OD (Box 344)
    - 2. Folder. OE-OH (Box 344)
    - 3. Folder. OI-ON (Box 344)
    - 4. Folder. OO-OT (Box 344)
    - 5. Folder. OU-OZ (Box 344)
    - 6. Folder. Overseas Press Club - Board of Governors (Box 344)
    - 7. Folder. Overseas Press Club - Miscellaneous (Box 344)
    - 8. Folder. PA-PD (Box 344)
    - 9. Folder. Palm Beach, Florida -Itinerary -, Feb. 17 (Box 344)
    - 10. Folder. PE-PH (Box 344)
    - 11. Folder. Penn, Jack (Box 344)
    - 12. Folder. Phil., Pa. - Itinerary - - Instrument Soc. of America, Sept. 15 (Box 344)
    - 13. Folder. Phillips, Herbert M., DDS (Box 344)
    - 14. [UNK] Phoenix, Arizona -Itinerary- Arizona Educ. Assoc., Oct. 31 (Box 344)
    - 15. [UNK] PI-PN (Box 344)
    - 16. [UNK] PO-PT (Box 344)
    - 17. [UNK] Pr inceton, N.J. - Itinerary- - "The Symposium", Sept. 15 (Box 344)
    - 18. [UNK] Providencs, R. I. - Itinerary- - R.I. Coll. of Educ. (receive Honorary [UNK], June 7 (Box 344)
    - 19. [UNK] PU-PZ (Box 344)
    - 20. [UNK] Purchase, N.Y. -Itinerary- - Amer. Friends Serv. Comm., April 19 (Box 344)
    - 21. [UNK] Perry, Mrs. R.J. (Box 344)
    - 22. [UNK] Q (Box 344)
  - Document Case #186 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1958
    - 1. Folder. RA-RD (Box 344)
    - 2. Folder. RE-RH (Box 344)
    - 3. Folder. Reader's Digest (Box 344)
    - 4. Folder. Reading, PA. Itinerary -, June 5 (Box 344)
    - 5. Folder. Reissner, Max -, 1954, 1957, 1958, 1959 (Box 344)
    - 6. Folder. Reynolds, Earle (Box 344)
    - 7. Folder. RI-RN (Box 344)
    - 8. Folder. RO-RT (Box 344)
    - 9. Folder. Rochelle Park, N.J. Itinerary - -UWF, March 31 (Box 344)
    - 10. Folder. Roper, Elmo (Box 344)
    - 11. Folder. RU-RZ (Box 344)
  - Document Case # 187 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1958
    - 1. Folder. SA-SD (Box 344)
    - 2. Folder. Sandler, Ake (Box 344)
    - 3. Folder. Satenstein, Sidney (Box 344)
    - 4. Folder. Scott, Michael (Box 344)
    - 5. Folder. Scribners (Box 344)
    - 6. Folder. SE-SH (Box 344)
    - 7. Folder. SI-SN (Box 344)
    - 8. Folder. Simon & Schus ter (Box 344)
    - 9. Folder. SO-ST (Box 344)
  - Document Case # 188 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1958
    - 1. Folder. Springfield, Mass. - Itinerary-, March 5 (Box 344)
    - 2. Folder. Stassen, Harold (Box 344)
    - 3. Folder. St. Louis, Missouri-Itinerary-, Feb. 23 (Box 344)
    - 4. Folder. Stamford - Low-Heywood-, June 4 (Box 344)
    - 5. Folder. Stamford - Itinerary-, Jan. 5 (Box 344)
    - 6. Folder. SU-SZ (Box 344)
    - 7. Folder. Summit, N.J. -, Jan. 9 (Box 344)
    - 8. Folder. Syracuse N.Y.-, Dec. 8 (Box 344)
    - 9. Folder. TA-TD (Box 344)
    - 10. Folder. Tampa, Florida-, Feb. 15 (Box 344)
    - 11. Folder. TE-TH (Box 344)
    - 12. Folder. Terre Haute, Ind.-, Jan. 23 (Box 344)
    - 13. Folder. Thornton, Monte (Box 344)
    - 14. Folder. TI-TN (Box 344)
    - 15. Folder. Tiffin, Ohio- Heidelberg Col. -, Sept. 25 (Box 344)
    - 16. Folder. TO-TT (Box 344)
    - 17. Folder. Town Hall-N.Y.C.-, April 9 (Box 344)
    - 18. Folder. TU-TZ (Box 344)
    - 19. Folder. Tulsa, Oklahoma-, May 27 (Box 344)
    - 20. Folder. Tuskegee Inst., Ala.-, May 26 (Box 344)
    - 21. Folder. Tytell, Martin (Box 344)
    - 22. Folder. U (Box 344)
    - 23. Folder. Union, N.J.-, October 4 (Box 344)
    - 24. Folder. United Air Lines (Box 344)
    - 25. Folder. U.A.L.- In Re (Box 344)
  - Document Case #189 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1958
    - 1. Folder. UWF -, 1958 (Box 344)
    - 2. Folder. UWF - Exec. Committee-, Oct. 28,1958 (Box 344)
    - 3. Folder. UWF - Exec. Committee-, Sept. 19,1958 (Box 344)
    - 4. Folder. UWF - Exec. Committee-, Dec.5,1958 (Box 344)
    - 5. UWF UWF - National Council-, Sept. 20, 1958 (Box 344)
    - 6. UWF UWF - National Council-, Dec. 6, 1958 (Box 344)
    - 7. UWF Vassar College (International Conference) (Box 344)
    - 8. UWF V (Box 344)
    - 9. UWF Y (Box 344)
    - 10. UWF Z (Box 344)
    - 11. UWF Viking Press (Box 344)
  - Document Case # 190 Personal and Business Correspondence (W-Z) and MISCELLANEOUS [UNK], (1950-1958)
    - 1. Folder. WA-WD -, 1958 (Box 345)
    - 2. Folder. Wallace, Mike -, 1958 (Box 345)
    - 3. Folder. Washington-- National War College-, May 26 (Box 345)
    - 4. Folder. Washington-- National Jewish Velfare Board-, April 19 (Box 345)
    - 5. Folder. Washington-- UWF-, Feb. 9 (Box 345)
    - 6. Folder. Washington-- All Souls' Church-, Feb. 9-a.m. (Box 345)
    - 7. Folder. WE-WH-, 1958 (Box 345)
    - [UNK] Folder. WI-WN -, 1958 (Box 345)
    - 9. Folder. Williamsport, Penna.-, April 17 (Box 345)
    - 10. Folder. Wilson, James (Re:) (Box 345)
    - 11. Folder. Wittcoff, Ray -, 1958 (Box 345)
    - [UNK] Folder. WU-WZ -, 1958 (Box 345)
  - Document Case # 191 Miscellaneous Correspondence, (1950-1958) (Box 345)
  - Document Case # 192 Personal and Business Correspondence (A-D)
    - 1. Folder. AB-AH-, 1959 (Box 346)
    - 2. Folder. AI-AN-, 1959 (Box 346)
    - 3. Folder. AO-AT-, 1959 (Box 346)
    - 4. Folder. Allen, Steve (Box 346)
    - 5. Folder. American Legion (Box 346)
    - 6. Folder. Albany, N.Y., -Oct. 16 (Box 346)
    - 7. Folder. Ann Arbor, Mich. -, March 13 (Box 346)
    - 8. Folder. Anonymous Letters (Box 346)
    - 9. Folder. Applications - Editorials (Box 346)
    - 10. Folder. Applications- Secretarial (Box 346)
    - 11. Folder. Applications - Miscellaneous (Box 346)
    - 12. Folder. Asia Society- India Committee (Box 346)
  - Document Case #193 Personal and Business Correspondence -, 1959
    - 1. Folder. Asia Society- Pakistan Committee (Box 346)
    - 2. Folder. As ia Society- Thailand Committee (Box 346)
    - 3. Folder. Asia Society - Miscellaneous (Box 346)
    - 4. Folder. Advertising- Complaints (Box 346)
    - 5. Folder. American Friends Service Comm.- Clarence Pickett (Box 346)
    - 6. Folder. American Friends Service Comm.- Miscellaneous (Box 346)
    - 7. Folder. Amherst- Material on Pres. Cole (Box 346)
    - 8. Folder. AU-AZ (Box 346)
    - 9. Folder. BA-BD (Box 346)
    - 10. Folder. BE-BH (Box 346)
    - 11. Folder. Berea, Ohio-, Jan. 29 (Box 346)
    - 12. Folder. Berkeley, Calif.-, Feb. 3,4,5 (Box 346)
    - 13. Folder. Bloomington, Ill. -, March 11-12 (Box 346)
    - 14. Folder. BI-BN (Box 346)
    - 15. Folder. BO-BT (Box 346)
  - Document Case #194 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. Bronxville, N.Y., Nov. 12 (Box 346)
    - 2. Folder. BU-BZ (Box 346)
    - 3. Folder. Buffalo, N.Y. -, Dec. 11 (Box 346)
    - 4. Folder. Benton, William (Box 346)
    - 5. Folder. Blake, Chris (Box 346)
    - 6. Folder. Briarcli ff (Box 346)
    - 7. Folder. Briskier, Dr. Arthur (Box 346)
    - 8. Folder. Burkhart, The Rev. Roy (Box 346)
    - 9. Folder. CA-CD (Box 346)
    - 10. Folder. Southern California-, Oct. 17-20 (Box 346)
    - 11. Folder. Cambridge, Mass.-, April 8 (Box 346)
    - 12. Folder. Cape Girardeau, Mo.-, Mar. 25 (Box 346)
    - 13. Folder. Cedarhurst, L.I.-, Jan.9 (Box 346)
    - 14. Folder. Chicago-, Nov. 24 (Box 346)
    - 15. Folder. CE-CH (Box 346)
    - 16. Folder. Chakovsky, Alexander (Box 346)
    - 17. Folder. CI-CN (Box 346)
    - 18. Folder. Claremont, Calif.-, Feb.14-15 (Box 346)
    - 19. Folder. Colgate Univ.-, April 13 (Box 346)
  - Document Case #195 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. Columbus, Ohio -, Jan. 28 (Box 346)
    - 2. Folder. Columbus, Ohio -, Feb. 24 (Box 346)
    - 3. Folder. CO-CT (Box 346)
    - 4. Folder. CU-CZ (Box 346)
    - 5. Folder. Complaints-Advts. and Circulation (Box 346)
    - 6. Folder. Complaints-Content (Box 346)
    - 7. Folder. Complaints-Editorial (Box 346)
    - 8. Folder. Commoner, Barry (Box 346)
    - 9. Folder. DA-DD (Box 346)
    - 10. Folder. DE-DH (Box 346)
    - 11. Folder. DI-DN (Box 346)
    - 12. Folder. DU-DZ (Box 346)
    - 13. Folder. Dearborn, Mich.-, 29 (Box 346)
    - 14. Folder. Dallas Conference (Box 346)
    - 15. Folder. Denver, Colorado -, Feb.19 (Box 346)
    - 16. Folder. Denver, Colorado, Oct. 23 (Box 346)
    - 17. Folder. Doubleday & Co. (Box 346)
    - 18. Folder. DO-DT (Box 346)
  - Document Case # 196 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. E.T.C. Correspondence #1. (Box 347)
    - 2. Folder. E.T.C. Correspondence #2. (Box 347)
    - 3. Folder. E.T.C. Miscellaneous (Box 347)
    - 4. Folder. E.T.R.C. -, Jan. 24 (Box 347)
    - 5. Folder. E.T.R.C. -, May 23 (Box 347)
    - 6. Folder. EA - ED (Box 347)
    - 7. Folder. EE - EH (Box 347)
    - 8. Folder. EI - EN (Box 347)
    - 9. Folder. EO -ET (Box 347)
    - 10. Folder. EU - EZ (Box 347)
    - 11. Folder. FA - FD (Box 347)
    - 12. Folder. FE - FH (Box 347)
    - 13. Folder. FI -FN (Box 347)
  - Document Case # 197 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. FO - FT (Box 347)
    - 2. Folder. FU - FZ (Box 347)
    - 3. Folder. Fahnestock, Samuel (Design Forecast) (Box 347)
    - 4. Folder. Fairfield, Conn. -, Jan. 15 (Box 347)
    - 5. Folder. Farmer, Edward Clifton (Box 347)
    - 6. Folder. Ferry, Barbara (Box 347)
    - 7. Folder. Freedom House (Box 347)
    - 8. Folder. Eriday Review Junior (Box 347)
    - 9. Folder. Friday Review (Box 347)
    - 10. Folder. Fund for the Republic (Box 347)
    - 11. Folder. GA - GD (Box 347)
    - 12. Folder. GE - GH (Box 347)
    - 13. Folder. GI - GN (Box 347)
  - Document Case #198 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. GO-GT (Box 347)
    - 2. Folder. GU-GZ (Box 347)
    - 3. Folder. General Electric (Box 347)
    - 4. Folder. Geneseo, N.Y. -, July 22 (Box 347)
    - 5. Folder. Grand Rapids -, Sept. 8 (Box 347)
    - 6. Folder. Great Neck, L.I. -, April 19 (Box 347)
    - 7. Folder. Great Neck, L.I. -, Oct. 2 (Box 347)
    - 8. Folder. HA-HD (Box 347)
    - 9. Folder. HE-HH (Box 347)
    - 10. Folder. HI-HN (Box 347)
  - Document Case #199 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. HO-HT (Box 347)
    - 2. Folder. HU-HZ (Box 347)
    - 3. Folder. Hall, Gordon #1 (Box 347)
    - 4. Folder. Hammill, J. Fund (Box 347)
    - 5. Folder. Harper & Bros. (Box 347)
    - 6. Folder. Heffner, Richard (Box 347)
  - Document Case # 200 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. II-IN (Box 348)
    - 2. Folder. India-Hisc. Corres. in Re& Corr. with Indians (Box 348)
    - 3. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAK- New York City A-M (Box 348)
    - 4. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAK- NEW YORK CITY N-Z (Box 348)
    - 5. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAKEALL OTHERS A-C (Box 348)
    - 6. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAKEALL OTHERS D-F (Box 348)
    - 7. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAKEALL OTHERS G-I (Box 348)
    - 8. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAKEALL OTHERS J-L (Box 348)
    - 9. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAKEALL OTHERS M-N (Box 348)
    - 10. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAKEALL OTHERS O-Q (Box 348)
    - 11. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAKEALL OTHERS R-T (Box 348)
    - 12. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAKEALL OTHERS U-W (Box 348)
    - 13. Folder. INVITATIONS TO SPEAKEALL OTHERS X-Z (Box 348)
  - Document Case # 201 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. Invitations-Keedick (Box 348)
    - 2. Folder. Non-Speaking Invitations-Not Accepted (New York City) (Box 348)
    - 3. Folder. Non-Speaking Invitations-Not Accepted (Box 348)
    - 4. Folder. Non-Speaking Invitations-Accepted (Box 348)
    - 5. Folder. Invitations to Speak-New York State-A-M (Box 348)
    - 6. Folder. Invitations to Speak-New York State-N-Z (Box 348)
    - 7. Folder. IO-IT (Box 348)
    - 8. Folder. IU-IZ (Box 348)
    - 9. Folder. JA-JD (Box 348)
    - 10. Folder. JE-JH (Box 348)
    - 11. Folder. JO-JT (Box 348)
    - 12. Folder. JU-JZ (Box 348)
    - 13. Folder. Japan (Box 348)
  - Document Case # 202 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. KA-KD (Box 348)
    - 2. Folder. KE-KH (Box 348)
    - 3. Folder. KI-KN (Box 348)
    - 4. Folder. KO-KT (Box 348)
    - 5. Folder. KU-KZ (Box 348)
    - 6. Folder. Keedick, Lee (Box 348)
    - 7. Folder. Kelly, Walt (Box 348)
    - 8. Folder. Knoof, Alfred, Inc. (Box 348)
    - 9. Folder. Kuh, Katherine - SR Art Critic (Box 348)
    - 10. Folder. LA-LD (Box 348)
    - 11. Folder. LE-LH (Box 348)
    - 12. Folder. LI-LN (Box 348)
  - Document Case # 203 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. LO-LT (Box 348)
    - 2. Folder. LU-LZ (Box 348)
    - 3. Folder. Las Vegas, Nev. -, Feb. 18 (Box 348)
    - 4. Folder. Levin, Martin (Box 348)
    - 5. Folder. Levittown Schools (Box 348)
    - 6. Folder. Loveman, Amy Award (Box 348)
    - 7. Folder. Louisville, Kentucky, March 26 (Box 348)
    - 8. Folder. Louisville, Kentucky, April 15 (Box 348)
    - 9. Folder. MA-MD (Box 348)
    - 10. Folder. ME-MH (Box 348)
    - 11. Folder. MI-MN (Box 348)
    - 12. Folder. MO-MT (Box 348)
    - 13. Folder. MU-MZ (Box 348)
  - Document Case # 204 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. Mac (Box 348)
    - 2. Folder. MC (Box 348)
    - 3. Folder. Macmillan Co. (Box 348)
    - 4. Folder. Mc Graw-Hill (Box 348)
    - 5. Folder. Maharajah of Mysore (Box 348)
    - 6. Folder. Mayers, Lawrence (Box 348)
    - 7. Folder. Medelman, Katherine (Box 348)
    - 8. Folder. Merrill Trust (Box 348)
    - 9. Folder. Miami, Fla. -, Nov. 17 (Box 348)
    - 10. Folder. Modisane, William (Box 348)
    - 11. Folder. Montclair, N.J. -, April 14 (Box 348)
  - Document Case # 205 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. NA-ND (Box 348)
    - 2. Folder. NE-NH (Box 348)
    - 3. Folder. NI-NN (Box 348)
    - 4. Folder. NO-NT (Box 348)
    - 5. Folder. NU-NZ (Box 348)
    - 6. Folder. N.A.A.C.P. (Box 348)
    - 7. Folder. National Air Lines (Box 348)
    - 8. Folder. National Planning Association (Box 348)
    - 9. Folder. Nationwide Insurance (Box 348)
    - 10. Folder. NATO-Nuclear (Box 348)
    - 11. Folder. N.E.T. (Box 348)
    - 12/ Folder. Teachers College of Connecticut -New Britain, Conn. (Box 348)
    - 13. Folder. New Brunswick, N.J., -Jan. 19 (Box 348)
    - 14. Folder. New Brunswick, N.J. -Rutgers Univ., -Oct. 28 (Box 348)
    - 15. Folder. New Haven, Conn., -May 5 (Box 348)
    - 16. Folder. New York, N.Y. - Associated Collegiate Press (Box 348)
    - 17. Folder. New York, N.Y. - Trinity Church (Box 348)
    - 18. Folder. OA-OD (Box 348)
    - 19. Folder. OE-OH (Box 348)
    - 20. Folder. OI-ON (Box 348)
    - 21. Folder. OO-OT (Box 348)
    - 22. Folder. OU-OZ (Box 348)
  - Document Case # 206 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. Oak Park-Ill., -Nov. 23 (Box 349)
    - 2. Folder. O'Brien, Hugh (Box 349)
    - 3. Folder. Olds, Glenn (Box 349)
    - 4. Folder. Oswego, N.Y., -April 30 (Box 349)
    - 5. Folder. Overseas Press Club- Board of Governors (Box 349)
    - 6. Folder. Overseas Press Club- Miscellaneous (Box 349)
    - 7. Folder. PA-PD (Box 349)
    - 8. Folder. PE-PH (Box 349)
    - 9. Folder. PI-PN (Box 349)
    - 10. Folder. PO-PT (Box 349)
    - 11. Folder. PU-PZ (Box 349)
    - 12. Folder. Patterson, N.J., -Jan. 13 (Box 349)
    - 13. Folder. Philadelphia, Pa., -May 11 (Box 349)
    - 14. Folder. Princeton, N.J. -UWF, -April 2 (Box 349)
    - 15. Folder. "Prominent People" (Box 349)
    - 16. Folder. Promotion (Box 349)
    - 17. Folder. Puerto Rico, -Nov. 14-15 (Box 349)
    - 18. Folder. "Pakistan People and Affairs" (Box 349)
    - 19. Folder. Prescott, [UNK] N. (Box 349)
    - 20. Folder. Provdence, R.T., -May 21 (Box 349)
    - 21. Folder. Provo, Utah, Feb. 2 (Box 349)
    - 22. Folder. Purchase, N.Y., April 24 (Box 349)
  - Document Case # 207 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. RA-RD (Box 349)
    - 2. Folder. RE-RH (Box 349)
    - 3. Folder. RI-RN (Box 349)
    - 4. Folder. RO-RT (Box 349)
    - 5. Folder. RU-RZ (Box 349)
    - 6. Folder. Reader's Digest (Box 349)
    - 7. Folder. Reissner, Max (Box 349)
    - 8. Folder. Reynolds, Earle (Box 349)
    - 9. Folder. Reynolds, Earle Fund (Box 349)
  - Document Case # 208 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. Russia - N.Y. - Paris - Warsaw, -June 10-16 (Box 349)
    - 2. Folder. Warsaw, -June 13-16 (Box 349)
    - 3. Folder. Russia - Moscow, -June 16- July 6 (Box 349)
    - 4. Folder. Russia Trip, -June 1959 (Box 349)
    - 5. Folder. Roper, Elmo (Box 349)
    - 6. Folder. Ritner, Peter (Box 349)
    - 7. Folder. Rochester, N.Y., April 16 (Box 349)
    - 8. Folder. Russia - After Effects (Box 349)
    - 9. Folder. Russia - Materials (Box 349)
  - Document Case # 209 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. SA-SD (Box 350)
    - 2. Folder. SE-SH (Box 350)
    - 3. Folder. SI-SN (Box 350)
  - Document Case # 210 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. SU-SZ (Box 350)
    - 2. Folder. Sandler, Abe (Box 350)
    - 3. Folder. Saginaw, Mich. -, Oct. 29 (Box 350)
    - 4. Folder. SANE- Misc. Material (Box 350)
    - 5. Folder. San Francisco-, Feb. 17 (Box 350)
    - 6. Folder. Saratoga Sorings, N.Y.-, April 29 (Box 350)
    - 7. Folder. Satenstein, Sidney (Box 350)
    - 8. Folder. Seattle, Wash.-, Feb. 6 (Box 350)
    - 9. Folder. Snyder, N.Y. -, March 6 (Box 350)
    - 10. Folder. Stanford, Calif.-, Feb. 16 (Box 350)
    - 11. Folder. Stevenson, Adlai-- Campaign (Box 350)
    - 12. Folder. Stone's Weekly (Box 350)
    - 13. Folder. TA-TD (Box 350)
    - 14. Folder. Tampa, Fla.-, March 19-20-21 (Box 350)
    - 15. Folder. Tampa Fund for World Sanity (Box 350)
    - 16. Folder. SO-ST (Box 350)
  - Document Case # 211 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. TE-TH (Box 350)
    - 2. Folder. Thornton, Monte (Box 350)
    - 3. Folder. (Box 350)
    - 4. Folder. TO-TT (Box 350)
    - 5. Folder. TU-TZ (Box 350)
    - 6. Folder. UA-UD (Box 350)
    - 7. Folder. UI-UN (Box 350)
    - 8. Folder. UO-UT (Box 350)
    - 9. Folder. United Air Lines (Mr. Patterson) (Box 350)
    - 10. Folder. U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Box 350)
    - 11. Folder. U.S. Information Agency (Box 350)
    - 12. Folder. U.W.F. (Box 350)
    - 13. Folder. U.W.F.-, Feb. 27-28-Mar.1 (Box 350)
    - 14. Folder. U.W.F. -, May 22-23-24 (Box 350)
  - Document Case # 212 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1959
    - 1. Folder. U.W.F. (Exec. Committee) (Box 350)
    - 2. Folder. U.W.F.- Exec. Comm.-, March 24 (Box 350)
    - 3. Folder. U.W.F.- Exec. Comm. -, April 28 (Box 350)
    - 4. Folder. U.W.F.National Council-, Sept. 19 (Box 350)
    - 5. Folder. U.W.F.National Council, Dec. 5 (Box 350)
    - 6. Folder. Viking Press (Box 350)
    - 7. Folder. VA-VD (Box 350)
    - 8. Folder. VE-VH (Box 350)
    - 9. Folder. VI-VN (Box 350)
    - 10. Folder. VO-VT (Box 350)
  - Document Case # 213 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1960
    - 1. Folder. AA-AD (Box 351)
    - 2. Folder. AE-AH (Box 351)
    - 3. Folder. AI-AN (Box 351)
    - 4. Folder. AO-AT (Box 351)
    - 5. Folder. AU-AZ (Box 351)
    - 6. Folder. Advertising- Miscellaneous (Box 351)
    - 7. Folder. Albany, N.Y. -, May 5, 1960 (Box 351)
    - 8. Folder. Allen, Steve (Box 351)
    - 9. Folder. Asia Society (Box 351)
    - 10. Folder. American Friends (Box 351)
    - 11. Folder. American Judaism (Box 351)
    - 12. Folder. Adelphi College-, June 15 (Box 351)
  - Document Case # 214 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1960
    - 1. Folder. Barkham, John-- Office (Box 351)
    - 2. Folder. BA-BD (Box 351)
    - 3. Folder. BE-BH (Box 351)
    - 4. Folder. BI-BN (Box 351)
    - 5. Folder. Applications (Box 351)
    - 6. Folder. B O-BT (Box 351)
  - Document Case # 215 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1960
    - 1. Folder. BU-BZ (Box 351)
    - 2. Folder. Reatty, Jerome - Office (Box 351)
    - 3. Folder. Bedient, Clarence (Box 351)
    - 4. Folder. Bowser, Hal- Office Memos (Box 351)
    - 5. Folder. CA-CD (Box 351)
    - 6. Folder. CE-CH (Box 351)
    - 7. Folder. CI-CN (Box 351)
  - Document Case # 216 Personal and Business Correspondence, 1960
    - 1. Folder. CO-CP (Box 351)
    - 2. Folder. CR-CT (Box 351)
    - 3. Folder. CU-CZ (Box 351)
    - 4. Folder. Carnegie Supplement (Box 351)
    - 5. Folder. Chadbourn, D. - Office (Box 351)
    - 6. Folder. Chapel Hill, N.S.-, Jan. 30-31 (Box 351)
    - 7. Folder. Chicago-Ill., Oct. 10-11 (Box 351)
    - 8. Folder. Chicago-SANE -, Oct. 14,15,16 (Box 351)
    - 9. Folder. Chicago Stadium-, Oct. 17 (Box 351)